Finding Aid for the Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature (TISL)
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series II: TISL General Assemblies
  - 32nd-33rd General Assemblies (Box 30)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, General Welfare (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, Higher Education (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, Internal Affairs/ Judiciary (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, State & Local Government (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, Transportation & Energy (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - 34th G.A. Notebook (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - 34th G. A. TISL Bills (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - 34th G. A. TISL Bills (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - 37th General Assembly (Box 31)
    - Full Time Enrollment (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 37th G.A. Bills 001-061 (Box 31)
  - 38th General Assembly (Box 32)
    - 38th G.A. General (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - TISL DAY 38th G.A. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Bluebook 38th G.A. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Manual 38th G.A. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - TISL Bills 38th G.A. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Bluebook 39th G.A. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - To Change the World 2008–CD (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Materials: Green TN Seal Folder
    - HJR 240 (Folder 1)
    - SJR 106 (Folder 2)